negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
I'm looking for
me
n
mmm
AHHHHHH!
We are A-U-C-K-Y!
We are the Breaktime Carrots of Weapons!
BTG Channel live streaming has started!
The theme this time is just before the first one-man live show! Economic Weekly on YouTube!
Yay!
How does everyone feel now that the long-awaited one-man live concert is coming up in two weeks?
Well, it's really early and I think the day will come in the blink of an eye.
No, it really is. I'm really nervous right now.
It's true, it's only two weeks away.
I really realize it.
It's only a month to go until the next day.
If it had been two months, you know.
There are only two weeks left.
It's so early.
Everyday on Twitter, they announce how many days are left.
The date is getting smaller and smaller, and I'm starting to realize that it's not looking good for me.That date is getting smaller and smaller, and I'm starting to realize that it's not good.
It's really too soon.
I started the countdown a month ago.
I thought, "Isn't it too early to start the countdown? I was thinking, "Well, we'll start it in about a week, so it's too soon.
I thought it was too early to start the countdown.
I was thinking it was so fast when the countdown started, but then I realized it was going to be in the single digits,
I thought, "This is not good.
I'm getting impatient.
So, this time, we'll hear about the members' passion for the one-man show and also open up the new information about the show,
I would like to share with you some new information about the live concert.
What's new?
What is it?
This is really good new information.
Really?
Are you sure?
Is there anyone who would say something that shouldn't be said in real life?
Be careful.
Like singing?
That's a very bad idea.
I'm the one who should do it, too.
Wait a minute.
You were whispering, so I don't think he heard you.
You didn't hear me.
You didn't hear me, did you?
No, I didn't hear you.
That means you didn't hear that.
I didn't say much.
You didn't.
The way you delivered it wasn't very good.
I really didn't say it.
I haven't said it.
I'm not saying it now.
You can't hear me, can you?You didn't hear me, did you?
I really don't.
Well, that's all I'm saying,
Today, I would like to get excited with you all for the one-man show.
Yes, that's right,
Now I'm taking dance lessons and practicing songs for the one-man show,
I think you are having a very hard day, taking dance lessons, practicing songs, and so on,
I think you have changed a lot of things. The lessons.
They have changed.
We are the only ones performing at the one-man show,
We play a lot of songs. More than usual.
That's why we need to strengthen our physical strength,
That's true.
Recently, in lessons, we have to run for the whole song.
It's tough, isn't it?
We also do things like repetitive dictation,
What was it again?
Doremifasorashido night.
Shuttle run.
Like a shuttle run,
Like a shuttle run from here to there.
It's tough, isn't it?
The lessons have increased, too.
We do a lot more muscle training than before, and everyone is working hard.
We had a lesson today, too.
Yes, we did. We are working hard.
I've been spending my days with such a tense atmosphere,
I'm sure everyone has their own ways to relax and unwind,
I would like to hear what you do to relax.
I would like to ask what you do to relax and what you do to relax.
Can I write about my oyster muscle, too?
I would like to ask each one of you to write and present your ideas one by one.
While everyone is writing, my way to relax is basically to eat.
I see.
I eat sweets and blow off all the fatigue.I eat sweets and blow off all the fatigue.
I love the anime, and I love the standby screen.
Just opening my phone is like taking a break and relaxing, and I enjoy it every day.
By the way, my favorite sweets are the famous Naruto kintoki, a specialty of Tokushima Prefecture, because I am from Tokushima Prefecture.
I want some too, Ai!
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'm not sure if it's cut into pieces or not, because everyone is expecting it to be cut into pieces.
No, I'm not! I'm serious!
Especially when it comes to birds.
Okay, I'll ask him to do it one more time.
Really?
Specific.
Well, I'm going to Grandma's house.
I understand this so much.
It's a nice mound.
It really heals and calms you down.
When I go to my grandma's house, you know, all kinds of things come out.
That's right!
The other day I drank something called Sakura-tea for the first time.
The kind with salt on the cherry blossoms?
Like salted?
You put it in hot water, and when you add hot water, the cherry blossoms bloom.
So cute!
It's so delicious, and lately I've been having it.
I'm in trouble.
But you're close with your grandma, right?
Yes, she is.
She said she was going on a date with her grandma.
That's right!
I said that quite a while ago.
I told her to make dumplings for her grandma at home.
If they were dumplings, she would get run over.
Like I carried them.
I dinged the dumplings at home, and since we are a family of four, we had five dumplings, which is eight dumplings.
I thought there was one left over, so I dinged it.
It would be better to have an extra one.Maybe I should have an extra.
Sweet.
I like kids, so I run along.
I see.
By going to grandma's house.
That's a good deal.
Who's next?
Me!
Oh!
Good girl!
Please!
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors first!
Yes!
Two then.
I win!
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's aiko, right?
Aiko, right?
Then, Misaki and Himaru, in that order.
Mine is Himaru is a bird.
Well, I would like Misaki to announce first.
What is Misaki's healing?
Misaki's healing is her mother's food.
Everyone's family is so nice.
Can you guess what this is?
Is it meat?
Yes, meat.
Meat?
Oh, a bear.
A bear.
Wait. Such balance.
Meat?
Cute.Cute.
I tried to put on expression.
It's cute.
Misaki likes meat rolls the best among her mother's meals.
She says so.
That's why I wanted to eat the meat rolls.
That's nice.
Eating mom's food heals me and makes me want to do my best in the lesson.
Everyone is too good?
I'm kind of sorry. On the contrary.
Conversely?
But maybe your mom is watching you on YouTube.
She's like, "Make me some more meat rolls.
Make me meat rolls.
She'll definitely make them for me.
But she often says she doesn't want to make them because it's too much work.
Is that so?
But I like you, so please do.
Please do.
I want to try it.
Then make it for everyone.
Wait, it's your mother's work.
It's not easy for a mother to design.
I'm counting on you.
Okay, then. String it up.
Next is Aoi.
You were adding a hook earlier.
Aoi's is se-o.
Playing with my dog.
I'm scared.
You're not scared.
There's a chestnut.
It's not a chestnut.
Aoi's dog.Aoi's dog.
Cat?
Sora-sora.
There's some kind of bump on his face.
Stop it.
See, I want to recreate it.
And the eyes.
I'm looking at the picture now, and I'm thinking, are those eyes? Maybe.
Is it?
What? Where's the eye?
I thought that was the eye.
That's an eyebrow.
It's an eyebrow.
Oh, that's what you mean?
They're distinctive.
I drew them.
When Aoi is very tired, Mona often plays with her.
That's why Mona has a toy called "Sensei" that she likes.
Sensei?
I like it so much that I bought a new one several times, and now I only have the last one,
He pulls out the cotton so many times,
I love him so much that I keep buying new ones, and now I only have the last one, but I keep pulling the cotton out and asking my mom to fix it,
I love her so much that she lets me play with her and Tomona.
By the way, do you have different breeds of dogs?
Sora is my grandma's dog,
Miniature Pinscher.
Heh... Pinscher.
Pinscher.
A tiny version of a police dog.
Oh, I see.
So they're really smart?
No, not at all.
Really?
That's what I'm saying.
Very much so.
I love sleeping and eating.I love to sleep and eat.
So they look alike.
Yeah. They look alike.
This is a smooth Chihuahua.
Why am I saying this?
I'm not sure anymore.
Smooth Chihuahua.
The sword is short.
Can I say something? Hi, Momari.
What? Sure.
Um, Mona here has seen Himari once.
Oh, yeah? I've seen her.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, I have. She was really cute.
And Mona was so scared of Himari.
She's touching her for the rest of her life.
I heard that dogs sleep with their owners.
Oh, really?
I was scared for the rest of my life.
Aoi said something scary about Himari.
I'm scared.
Himari is so scary.
What? What?
I'm scared.
Suddenly I'm scared.
Is that why you're scared, Mona?
That's right.
You're lying.
You were so cute.
That's not good. Even Aoi's dog is messing with you. Himari.
That's a great story.
Yes, it is. For now, I'm playing with my dog.
So you've been playing with birds, right?
I'm sorry, but...I know it's extremely rude.
I didn't think it would be the last time.
Himari only bought a drawing.
Oh, wow.
But you like Himari's drawings lately, don't you?
But, you know, the picture on Himari's desk is a little too bad,
I haven't been able to draw.
Oh, I see.
That's why I want you to come with me to clean up.
It's not that clean.
Please.
You might not like it.
I don't want to.
Misaki's paintings are messy too.
Then, Aoi's.
Aoi's is fine.
What about you, Arisa?
Arisa too.
But...
Wait.
I can't help it.
Is there anyone here?
Is there anyone?
Is there anyone who is a germophobe or something?
I mean, if you're a germaphobe, come on in.
It's like everyone's a freak.
I'm glad you're here.
Do you have a particular favorite thing to draw?
I mean, I used to draw pictures of pretty girls.
I mean, I used to draw pictures of pretty girls, and he used to draw a portrait of us at the Valentine's Day party.
He was so good at it.
That was amazing.
I became a big fan of hers.
I really did.
Only one of them was a pro.
I like to draw, so at that time.I like to draw then.
I've been drawing since I was a little girl.
Since I was born.
I was born with a pencil.
That's how much I like it.
I think I've made a little use of that.
I see.
I'm going to do my best, and I'm going to do it at times like this.
I have to clean it up, and I have to do it quickly.
I didn't think so.
Then, first of all, please clean up so that you can have time without healing.
I will do my best.
So that was the way of healing and relaxation for everyone.
It was a good time.
The next theme was,
I would like to ask you what you would like to reward yourself with after the one-man show.
Reward.
I see.
I think it's a bit similar to the healing I mentioned earlier,
I think it's a bit similar to the healing I mentioned earlier, but everyone is really into the one-man show, and everyone is nervous, right?
So I'm sure everyone is wondering what they will do after the show,
So I would like to ask them.
I'd like to hear what they do afterwards.
I'm going to go out.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I want to sleep a lot after the one-man show.
You want to sleep a lot?
I want to sleep a lot.
I'll sleep a lot without worrying about anything.
I'll probably have some sweets, but I'll probably watch anime.
Have you already done that?
I did!
That was fast!
Can I say this?
I've been saying this for a long time, but there's one thing I really want to do after the one-man show,I have been saying this for a long time, but there is one thing I definitely want to do after the one-man show,
I want to go eat 10 yen bread.
I know!
That's a given, isn't it?
The kind that is mixed in.
Do you know about 10 yen buns, Mr. Kobayashi?
Do you know it?
I'll explain what it is.
It's a bread in the shape of a ten-yen coin,
It has cheese inside,
It's shaped like a 10 yen, but there's cheese inside, and it's really stretchy.
Airi loves bread so much and cheese so much.
It's great.
It's really great.
It's almost like a sponge cake,
It's not sponge cake.
It's like a fluffy zaribah?
It's like a sponge cake.
It's like a sponge cake, that's why it's so delicious.
I see.
But I've seen a lot of them on TikTok.
Wait a minute. Why is that?
What's with the hiragana?
I made a mistake.
I made a serious mistake.
Wait a minute.
I made a mistake.
That's right.
I really wanted to go out to eat,
He really wanted to go out to eat, and when he was done, he ate about five of them.
That's great.
I want to go out to eat with everyone.
Yeah, that's great.
Next up,
Can we make a connection?
I want to eat.It's like eating.
I could tell the first time I saw it.
Next.
The order in which they lost next.
You mean it's the same?
That's what it means.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Short Cody, right?
It doesn't matter anymore. I don't know which one you want.
Well, if you lose, be happy.
Yes, sir.
The loser first?
From the loser.
Don't be sad.
I understand.
I'll take care of it.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors!
Yay!
Himari first?
Himari first.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Which one?
Yay!
I lost.
Himari, Aoi, and Misaki, in that order.
I really lost.
Next up,
I'll go next. Himari..,
We're going to have dinner with the members!
I want to go!
It's a reward for myself, but I want to involve everyone.
Thank you.
By the way, what are we going to eat?By the way, what are you going to eat?
Monja.
I want to go!
Seriously, doesn't everyone love monja?
Everyone loves monja.
I want to eat sushi.
That's Himari's hobby.
Himari's favorite food is sushi.
Everybody likes sushi, right?
I do.
Don't you?
I wanted to go out for dinner with everyone.
I'd like that.
I want to go.
If we're going to do monja, next time we'll be successful.
I don't remember ever being able to do it right, do you?
You should be able to do it.
But monja is always a mess.
That's true.
You have to mix it, right?
All the flavors and aromas.
It was delicious.
As a result, it was not a success.
Himari is a master of monja.
Thank you very much.
No one has said that.
Next, Aoi.
Next, Aoi,
We're all staying at the Mede Chun's house.
This is good. It's so good.
I love Mede's house too much, don't you?
I love it.
I've never been there,
It's always been everyone's dream, right?
Dreams, you know, from you.Dreams, you know, from you.
I don't know if you expected me to do so much, but I really don't have anything.
MisakiI can imagine.
What kind of life I can live.
I think I'd be okay with that if you expected a lot from me.
What kind of stuff do you have?
You have a rice field, right? Nearby.
Yes, there is.
You have rice paddies and mountains, right?
Yes, but...
Well, then, let's all go into the rice paddies,
We can't go in there without permission.
We can observe insects and so on.
Unexpectedly.
We can do something we don't usually do, can't we?
That's what I mean.
I understand.
Maybe we can bury ourselves in the field.
We could dig up some potatoes.
Potatoes.
Digging for potatoes.
I want to dig.
So we have to think about the right time of year?
Yes, that's right.
What kind of food do they serve at Nerichinchi?
What? I'm curious.
Regular rice?
But they grow vegetables like a home garden,
Natsu and the others never buy vegetables,
You know, everyone says they like tomatoes.
Everyone in this group really likes tomatoes,
We are in a desperate situation because we have to eat tomatoes,
It's not that I want to eat them, it's just that I have to eat them,
And then, as if with a real passion, a bowl of tomatoes was served to us with a bang,
It was a dream.
It was a dream. Each one of us had to eat at least five tomatoes.Each person was supposed to get at least 5 pieces.
They were served on an amazing tour.
It's a dream come true.
Can I ask them to make the most of the season?
Sure, let's have everyone consume them.
I'm totally fine with it.
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm sure I can eat it.
I want to have a tomato eating championship.
I'm sure I can win.
Super ball.
I'm sure I can do it.
We've got button pots.
I can do it.
I can eat it.
Really?
Don't they serve vegetables, like fish?
I eat it once in a while.
Eat?
But Tokushima is close to the sea, so the fish is very delicious.
I eat sashimi.
Do you put sudachi on sashimi?
Yes, I do.
That's right.
I've never had lemon.
Do you usually put lemon on sashimi?
Don't they put it on sashimi?
Only soy sauce.
Just soy sauce.
I can't believe it.
It definitely has to have sudachi.
You mean you only put sudachi on it?
Sudachi and soy sauce.
Is that what you mean?
It's so refreshing.It's refreshing.
It's so delicious. It's so refreshing.
I want to eat this too.
I want to go there.
Everyone looks at me like I'm crazy.
I want to go.
I'll call my mom.
I'll consider it.
Please do.
Please give me Nemi-kunchi as a reward for my man-man.
It's already confirmed.
Next, Misaki, please.
Yes, I will.
Risa..,
We're going to Disneyland.
I want to go.
This is the last of Man-Man in Tokyo, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I want to go to Disneyland with the members on the next day.
It's a great idea.
It's a great chance.
It's so close.
We'll go there.
But aren't you guys tired? Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's like another stomach.
Like another stomach.
It's like everyone can really ride the attractions.
We can.
I can't.
Impossible?
I'll leave you to it.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Stay in line.
I want you to go with me to the line.Go with me to the line.
I want to be with you.
I want to ride with you.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll take you instead of you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll make him get over it.
Hey, let him hold your hand for a minute, and he'll get over it.
I'll do that.
He'll take you with him.
Oh, my God. What's with the face?
It's kind of soothing.
Part of me wants to get over it, but..,
I just don't have the courage.
You'll be fine. Once you get on it, you'll be fine.
It's like you overcame it for a while.
Yes, I did.
My friend forced me to ride with him.
Then you have a chance.
But you'll be fine if you go on it.
I have a scary image of Disney attractions.
Really?
The Disney attraction, Tower of Terror.
Misaki loves that one.
Is that the one with the silicone toons?
I can't remember the name. She explained it to me,
They explained about the elevator and the setting.
It was really scary, that explanation.
Really?
I kept scratching my ears.
The first explanation was too scary.
Yes, I almost cried there.
I almost cried.
That's what I'm afraid of.
After the ride.After the ride.
Himari, you rode in Mie, right?
Mie, Mie, huh?
We rode in Mie, didn't we?
Did I get on? What?
We boarded at Mie.
Wait, something like that, a long time ago,
You posted on your blog or something that you went there.
Yeah, after my friend Ogi confessed to me,
I went there with my family.
I see.
To the amusement park.
I didn't get to ride until then.
Then I stopped going for a while, and there was a gap of time, so I couldn't ride anymore.
Then you can still ride.
No, I can't. I can't. I really can't.
It's been a while.
I'm just in time for Haridori at Universe.
It's OK.
I'm just about to say, "OK.
Don't worry, I have everyone's back.
That's right.
Once you get on board, you win.
If you force me to raise my hand, I'll remember it.
I want to raise my hand.
Oh no. It's really bad.
You must go.
I want to go, but I'll be watching from below.
What? Why?
You're forcing me to go.
Now that we've talked a lot, here's the new information about the one-man show you've all been waiting for!
New information!
It came out of nowhere.
It came suddenly, didn't it?
All kinds of new information about the new one-man-mai.
I'd like to share with you some information that I have never announced before.I would like to share with you here some information that I have not presented at all before.
It's fun.
We've been waiting for this for a long time, and so have you,
Oh my God,
What are we going to do?
Oh, my God,
What a surprise,
We will be selling the long-awaited Breaktime Girls merchandise!
Please wait.
Thank you for your patience.
You've been waiting a long time.
I talked to fans at every event,
I've been talking to fans at every event, and they're like, "Where are the goods?
I was getting a lot of comments like, "Where are the goods? I'm sure you're right.
That's for sure.
My mom asked me many times.
She also asked me if the merchandise has come out yet.
BTG merchandise? She kept asking me,
I can finally say that it's coming out.
I'm so happy. Thank you very much.
It was fun.
What kind of goods are they?
And we have the real thing this time!
It's wonderful.
Let's show you the makeup.
I like it.
Aren't you all excited right now?
Excited.
It's not good.
Well, first of all, I'd like to announce what Misaki has in her possession.
The first item is..,
T-shirt!
Speaking of goods, I think it's a T-shirt.It's like when it comes to merchandise.
It's a classic.
It says BTG on it,
It also has the Heart Clash logo on it.
It's cute.
I think it's a pretty cool design.
So it can be worn by men and women of all ages,
and easy to wear.
We even have large sizes.
There is a wide range of sizes.
Misaki wears a large size,
She wears an XL size,
I'd like to wear a large size with a loose fit.
It's cute.
She's so cute.
She's cool and cute.
I want her to wear it to live shows.
That's true.
Maybe a live T-shirt.
It would be great if everyone wore them.
I'd be so happy.
They might get excited and start sweating,
So please bring your fingers, too.
There are also ones for your hair.
Or for sleeping.
We also need memorials, right?
For sure.
Decorate.
That's what I'm talking about.
It was the first one.
It was.
T-shirt.
It's nice.
Please wear it, everyone.
Please buy it before the concert.
Wear it at the concert.Wear it at the live.
Next, Himari, please.
What's the one you're holding?
Seino.
Ta-da!
It's a muffler towel.
Scarf towel.
Unlike the cool design we had earlier,
I added a little bit of cute pink,
It's a nice touch.
It's really cute.
It's cute.
Here,
The members' names,
Each member's name is written here.
Isn't it so cute?
I'm so happy about the names.
They also commented on the towels.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Please write your name in this stream.
Write the member's name,
Try it on the sixth person.
Please do it.
You will be the new daughter of the heart.
We're going to have a live concert.
Yes, you're right.
I can wipe it with my hand,
You can wipe it with your hand and swing it around if you want.
It's a good idea.
It's true.
It feels like a live performance.
Be careful not to hit the person next to you.
It's cute.
By all means.By all means.
Isn't it cute?
It was my favorite muffler towel.
Ta-da!
Yes, it is. Next,
Aoi will introduce..,
Three, two, one!
Dadaaan!
Asari desand.
So cute.
Here's another one,
It's got a striped pattern,
Breaktime Girls!
itself is good.
It's cool.
This is cool,
This person, each member of the group,
If you spot each person, each member, on the bottom of this thing,
the bottom of the stand can be used as a stand for decoration,
It also has a ball chain attached to it,
And there's also a ball chain attached to it,
and this member,
I want you to put it on your bag, lipstick, and so on,
I'd like you to put it on your bag, lipstick, etc.
Like a good luck charm or something.
I thought it would be a nice touch.
It's cute.
Like you can take the members on a trip or something.
That's for sure.
If this mini blue thing was peeking out of the bag..,
It would be so cute.
And please promote it, too.
Please put it in your bag like this.
Please fill it up like this.
It's an acrylic stand.
It's so cute.It's so cute.
Cute.
Pink.
I love it so much.
Mizuki's favorite acrylic stand.
I want all of them.
I want to look at them too.
I'd like that too, please, everyone.
It was an acrylic stand.
Lastly, Arisa introduces..,
Arisa is going to introduce..,
Penlight.
Yay.
Speaking of which.
This is it. Really.
We got a penlight.
I'm so happy. This is it.
It's round and cute.
I'm going to make it shine.
It comes in three colors.
What's the first one?
Pink.
That's nice.
Pink,
It's like heart-crush.
The color of heart-crush.
Next is red.
Red.
The color of BTG.
The color of Longo.
Pretty.
Next is white.
Very bright.
Cute.
I like this one a lot.I love this so much.
It says BTG here too,
It's so cute.
It's simple, but..,
It's simple, but it has a cute design, don't you think?
The circle is cute.
Transparent.
I like the design.
It's cute.
It looks good.
Wouldn't it be so beautiful if this was bubbling all over the venue?
Nice view.
It would be more beautiful if the colors were unified.
I wish they would unify the colors of the venue.
When BTG enters the venue...,
I'd like to see a sticker with the BTG entrance.
Can I ask for it?
Sure.
I would like to ask everyone who is watching us right now.
Have them spread all over the venue.
What color would you like?
I wonder what color.
I'm thinking pink, since it's a heartcrush.
Because Longo's color is pink.
Pink.
That would be so cute.
So, if everything is pink when BTG comes in.
If they were pink, it would mean that all of you who are watching now have spread the word.
That's what it means.
If I had a white coat, I would call it pink pink pink.
I'll let you say it secretly.
I don't even want to call it pink at first.
Please do.
I'll be impressed.
I really am.
I'm looking forward to it.I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so looking forward to it. Let's see it now.
I'm counting on you all.
Promise.
Finger cutting game.
If you lie, Arisenbornose.
I cut off my finger.
I'll make a promise without your permission.
This way without permission.
I'm looking forward to it.
So, here are the goods.
They are all so cute.
Please check them out, everyone.
Please do.
I'm so happy. I'm really glad.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You guys must be surprised.
Really?
It was all so cute.
I hope you're happy with it.
I wanted to.
I'm glad.
Come here.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I'll buy them all.
You'll buy them all?
Complete.
Complete?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's been a while.
It's been a long time since I've seen you guys in recovery.It's been a long time since I've been able to see everyone in recovery.
It's been a long time.
Thank you very much.
We are looking forward to it.
Kiito said he was going out.
No kidding.
Please spread the word.
I want you to take them on picnics and stuff.
Please put it up as a wall. I'll make sure.
I'm sure the members' souls are in it.
Please take good care of them.
Please.
And the content of the benefit event has also been decided.
First of all, Osaka.
The first part of the Osaka event will be an air high-touch session,
the second part is a stay-together session.
It's right after the concert, right?
I guess so.
I can't wait to hear what you think.
I'm really curious. That kind of thing.
Please give me lots of compliments.
Will you work that hard?
I'll do my best.
And for those in Tokyo, part one is the stay-together shot session,
The second part will be an air high-touch session and a shot session for all the members.
I'm sure this will be a lot of fun,
Please come and join us.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all there.
The first one-man live concert is only two weeks away,
It's really just before the show, and it's getting closer.
So, I would like to ask each one of you for your final thoughts or enthusiasm.
From Cape.
Finally, the goods that I have longed for are now on sale,
I'm already wrapping this towel around my neck and twirling it around,
Let's enjoy it together.
I will practice hard.I will practice hard.
I'll do my best.
I'll be there then.
I'll definitely bring you a fun live show, so please look forward to it.
Wow!
You haven't?
Okay, next, Aoi Neri and
Megan's one-man-knife.
Let's have fun together!
Nice voice. Let's have fun!
The tension is like a live performance already.
That's true.
Okay, next up is Yuri.
This is my first one-man knife show, so...
Let's wave these penlights and get excited together!
I'm looking forward to it.
The last net.
Yes, it's the first one-man live performance, and it's only going to happen once.
Let's make it a great memory together!
Let's make it a great memory!
Let's do our best!
I'm getting nervous thinking that it's really in a week.
A week?
Really?
I'm nervous.
It's too soon.
I hope everyone has a good time.
Everyone is working hard right now, so let's continue to work hard until the show.
Yes, I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
And, you know, next week on March 19, we will be performing at the opening act of Iginari Tohoku Sun.
I will be the opening act for Iginari Tohoku Sun!
Let's do our best!
Thank you very much!
If you will be there, I hope you will be able to see how Berryz KOBO will perform!If you will be there, I hope you will be able to see how Berryz KOBO will perform!
I'll definitely make it exciting!
Let's get excited!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
I'm so happy to see you again.
And on April 16th, we will be having our free event in Osaka!
It's the first free event for the one-man-issue, isn't it?
Isn't that in about a week?
Soon.
Soon, right?
Pretty soon.
I'm happy to see you again.
There's still the hospital. I'm sure we can do it in a week.
I'm sure we'll give you our best performance.
I'm sure you'll be in high spirits.
BTG, I'm sure you'll have a lot to look forward to.
You'll be able to see a lot of them.
So please come and see us!
Yes, please.
And there will be another radio show at 8:00, so please come!
Please come.
Please come!
So, our first one-man show is coming up in two weeks,
If you haven't bought a ticket yet, please do so and come to the show.
If you haven't bought a ticket yet, please buy one and come to the show.
If you haven't bought a ticket yet, please buy one and come see us.
We will give you a hot live show that you won't regret, so please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
Please wait for us!
Your voice is so loud.
Really loud.
I've been saying "back-back-back" a bit.
I'm doing it myself.
So, please look forward to it.Yes, so you can all look forward to it.
Enjoy!
That's all for us,
A-U-C-K-Y!
Lakina! Breaktime Girls!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
Squash time!
Wait for me!
Mmm.
Mmm...
Mnh-mnh.
Hm?
mmm